http://www.lsureveille.com/site/privacy.html

|
SEC COVID-19 Case Counts: Mississippi State University: no data
|
SEC COVID-19 Case Counts: University of South Carolina: 3,152
|
University of Tennessee: no data
|
University of Texas at Austin: 1,607 | Texas A&M University: 4,141
|
Vanderbilt University: 816
This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally Identifiable Information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other details to help you with your experience.When do we collect information?We collect information from you when you place an order or enter information on our site.How do we use your information?We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:• To quickly process your transactions.How do we protect your information?Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.We do not use Malware Scanning.Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order to maintain the safety of your personal information.All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.Do we use 'cookies'?We do not use cookies for tracking purposesYou can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since each browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.If you turn cookies off, some features will be disabled that make your site experience more efficient and may not function properly.However, you will still be able to place orders.Third-party disclosureWe do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when its release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property or safety.However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.Third-party linksWe do not include or offer third-party products or services on our website.GoogleGoogle's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=enWe use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.We have implemented the following:• Demographics and Interests ReportingWe, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.Opting out:Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page or by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.California Online Privacy Protection ActCalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require any person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting Personally Identifiable Information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals or companies with whom it is being shared. - See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpufAccording to CalOPPA, we agree to the following:Users can visit our site anonymously.Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum, on the first significant page after entering our website.Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy' and can easily be found on the page specified above.You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes:• On our Privacy Policy PageYou can change your personal information:• By emailing usHow does our site handle Do Not Track signals?We honor Do Not Track signals and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?It's also important to note that we allow third-party behavioral trackingCOPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States' consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.Fair Information PracticesThe Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:We will notify you via email• Within 7 business daysWe also agree to the Individual Redress Principle which requires that individuals have the right to legally pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.CAN SPAM ActThe CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.We collect your email address in order to:• Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders.To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:• Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.• Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.• Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.• Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.• Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.• Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us atstudentmedia@lsu.edu and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Website. These companies may use information (not including any Personally-Identifying Information) about your visits to the Website and other websites that are contained in Web Cookies in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Using a tool created by the Network Advertising Initiative, you can opt out of several third-party ad servers' and networks' Web Cookies simultaneously. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please complete the following links:   http://networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp,   http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/, or http://www.aboutads.info/choices/. Please contact us if you would like to know the identity of the third-party advertising companies we are currently using to serve ads.We may allow advertisers to choose the characteristics of users who will see their advertisements, and we may use any of the Non-Personally Identifying Information we have collected (including information you may have decided not to show to other users, such as your birth year or other sensitive personal information or preferences) to select the appropriate audience for those advertisements. We do not identify you to the advertiser.Contacting UsIf there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.www.lsunow.comB39 Hodges HallBaton Rouge, LA 70803U.S.A.studentmedia@lsu.edu
Anonymous Tips Form
Submit questions and anonymous tips here.
with a link to confirm list signup.
Error! There was an error processing your request.
LSU Reveille News Update
Twice-weekly updates on the latest news at LSUReveille.com. Sign up today!
Please enter a valid email address.
Wind:
Clear to partly cloudy. Low 52F. Winds light and variable.
Tonight
Clear to partly cloudy. Low 52F. Winds light and variable.
Tomorrow
Partly to mostly cloudy. High 73F. Winds SSE at 10 to 15 mph.
UpcomingRadar7 Day
Dense Fog Advisory from 2AM CST FRI until 9AM CST FRI
Weather Alert
...DENSE FOG ADVISORY IN EFFECT FROM 2 AM TO 9 AM CST FRIDAY...
* WHAT...VISIBILITY ONE QUARTER MILE OR LESS IN DENSE FOG.
* WHERE...ALL OF SOUTHWEST MISSISSIPPI AND COASTAL MISSISSIPPI.
PORTIONS OF SOUTHEAST LOUISIANA MAINLY ALONG AND NORTH OF THE
I-12 CORRIDOR.
* WHEN...FROM 2 AM TO 9 AM CST FRIDAY.
* ADDITIONAL DETAILS...A DENSE FOG ADVISORY MEANS VISIBILITIES
WILL FREQUENTLY BE REDUCED TO LESS THAN ONE QUARTER MILE.
PRECAUTIONARY/PREPAREDNESS ACTIONS...
IF DRIVING, SLOW DOWN, USE YOUR HEADLIGHTS, AND LEAVE PLENTY OF
DISTANCE AHEAD OF YOU.
Mostly clear. Lows overnight in the low 50s.
Clear to partly cloudy. Low 52F. Winds light and variable.
Partly cloudy. Highs in the low 70s and lows in the low 60s.
A few showers in the evening becoming a steady rain overnight. Thunder possible. Low 62F. Winds S at 10 to 15 mph. Chance of rain 80%.
Times of sun and clouds. Highs in the low 70s and lows in the upper 40s.
A few clouds from time to time. Low 49F. Winds light and variable.
Showers possible. Highs in the upper 60s and lows in the mid 40s.
Mostly cloudy with rain ending overnight. Low 44F. Winds NW at 10 to 15 mph. Chance of rain 70%. Rainfall near a quarter of an inch.
Times of sun and clouds. Highs in the mid 50s and lows in the low 40s.
Partly cloudy. Low 41F. Winds light and variable.
Partly cloudy. Highs in the low 60s and lows in the low 40s.
Rain showers early with clearing later at night. Low 41F. Winds WNW at 5 to 10 mph. Chance of rain 40%.
Mix of sun and clouds. Highs in the mid 50s and lows in the mid 30s.
Mostly clear skies. Low 36F. Winds light and variable.
© Copyright 2020 The Reveille, B-16 Hodges Hall LSU Baton Rouge, LA | Terms of Use | Privacy Policy
Powered by BLOX Content Management System from TownNews.com.
